She won't rest until she gets justice
Fugitive at 17 is a tv movie, crime, mystery film directed by Jim Donovan.
Suspected of murdering her best friend, a teenage
computer-hacker goes on the run to find the real killer.
Holly Hamilton, played by Marie Avgeropoulos.
Detective Cameron Langford, played by Christina Cox.
Spencer Oliphant, played by Casper Van Dien.
Detective Roger West, played by Danny Blanco Hall.
Dan Dalton, played by Daniel Rindress-Kay.
Captain Tony Ashler, played by Frank Schorpion.
The Fugitive is a 1993 American action thriller film, directed by Andrew Davis, with a script
co-written by Jeb Stuart and David Twohy, from a previous story draft which Twohy had written.
Based on the 1960s TV series, itself loosely inspired by the trial of Sam Sheppard, the film stars
Harrison Ford, Tommy Lee Jones, Sela Ward, Joe Pantoliano, Andreas Katsulas, and Jeroen Krabbé.
After being framed for the murder of his wife and
sentenced to death, vascular surgeon Dr.
Richard Kimble (Ford) escapes from custody following a bus crash.
Kimble sets out to find the real killer and clear his name,
while being hunted by the police and a team of U.S.
marshals, led by Deputy Samuel Gerard (Jones).
The Fugitive premiered in Westwood, California, on July 29, 1993, and
was released in the United States on August 6, 1993.
It was a critical and commercial success, spending six weeks as the number-one film in the United
States, and grossing nearly $370 million worldwide against a $44 million budget.
It was the third-highest-grossing film of 1993 worldwide, with an
estimated 44 million tickets sold in the United States.
It was nominated for seven Academy Awards, including Best
Picture; Tommy Lee Jones won for Best Supporting Actor.
It was followed by the 1998 film U.S.
Marshals, in which Jones reprised his role as Deputy Marshal Sam
Gerard, along with some others of his earlier marshals team.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.